Class of 1985 Records, 1981-[ongoing]
Smith College Archives
Class of 1985 Records
1981-[ongoing]
Smith College. Class of 1985.
RG 80
3 boxes (1 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1985.
Historical Note
The Class of 1985 was the 107th graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1985 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1985, including materials from commencement, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, programs, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1985 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- General 1981 (Box 2289, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1985 (Box 2289, Folder 2)
- Ivy Day 1985 (Box 2289, Folder 3)
- Reunion 1990 (Box 2289, Folder 4)
- Reunion 1995 (Box 2289, Folder 5)
- Reunion 2000 (Box 2289, Folder 6)
- Reunion 2005 (Box 2289, Folder 7)
- Yearbook Photographs (Box 2290)
  - Candids 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 1)
  - Candids 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 2)
  - Candids 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 3)
  - Faculty 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 4)
  - Organizations 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 5)
  - Senior Photographs
    - A 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 6)
    - B 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 7)
    - C 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 8)
    - D 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 9)
    - E 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 10)
    - F 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 11)
    - G 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 12)
    - H 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 13)
    - I 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 14)
    - J 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 15)
    - K 1985 (Box 2290, Folder 16)
    - L 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 1)
    - M 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 2)
    - N 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 3)
    - O 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 4)
    - P-Q 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 5)
    - R 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 6)
    - S 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 7)
    - T 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 8)
    - U-V 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 9)
    - W 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 10)
    - Y-Z 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 11)
- Unidentified 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 12)
- Photographs Not Used 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 13)
- Rotner Proofs 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 14)
- Contact Sheets 1985 (Box 2291, Folder 15)